<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Corona</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">COVID19</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Corona Pandemic Information and Awareness</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">For more info visit mohfw.gov.in</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="menu_faq">FAQ</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="menu_tools">Tools</string>
    <string name="menu_share">Share</string>
    <string name="menu_send">Send</string>
    <string name="title_activity_faq">FAQ</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="faqdetails">
        Exposing yourself to the sun or to temperatures higher than 25C degrees DOES NOT prevent the coronavirus disease (COVID-19)
         MB_sun exposure \n

You can recover from the coronavirus disease (COVID-19). Catching the new coronavirus DOES NOT mean you will have it for life.

        \n\n\n
        Being able to hold your breath for 10 seconds or more without coughing or feeling discomfort DOES NOT mean you are free from the coronavirus disease (COVID-19) or any other lung disease.
        
        \n\n\n

Drinking alcohol does not protect you against COVID-19 and can be dangerous

        \n\n\n
        COVID-19 virus can be transmitted in areas with hot and humid climates
\n\n\n
        Cold weather and snow CANNOT kill the new coronavirus.
\n\n\n
        Taking a hot bath does not prevent the new coronavirus disease
\n\n\n
        The new coronavirus CANNOT be transmitted through mosquito bites.
\n\n\n
        Hand dryers are not effective in killing the 2019-nCoV. To protect yourself against the new coronavirus, you should frequently clean your hands with an alcohol-based hand rub or wash them with soap and water. Once your hands are cleaned, you should dry them thoroughly by using paper towels or a warm air dryer.
\n\n\n
        Spraying alcohol or chlorine all over your body will not kill viruses that have already entered your body
\n\n\n
        




    </string>
</resources>
